(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
hololive production COUNTDOWN LIVE 2024▷2025
せーの！
Ready, go!
皆さん、こんばんはー！
Everyone, good evening!
ホロライブプロダクション カウントダウンライブ 2024▷2025
hololive production COUNTDOWN LIVE 2024▷2025
スタートー！
Start!
概要欄から今すぐダウンロード！
Download now from the description box!
2017.09.07
2018.10.16
2021.01.20
2023.03.18
2023.12.15
2024.02.06
ときのそら / ロボ子さん / さくらみこ / AZKi
Tokino Sora / Roboco-san / Sakura Miko / AZKi
アキ・ローゼンタール / 夏色まつり / 白上フブキ / 赤井はあと
Aki Rosenthal / Natsuiro Matsuri / Shirakami Fubuki / Akai Haato
湊あくあ / 紫咲シオン / 百鬼あやめ / 癒月ちょこ / 大空スバル
Minato Aqua / Murasaki Shion / Nakiri Ayame / Yuzuki Choco / Oozora Subaru
大神ミオ / 猫又おかゆ / 戌神ころね
Ookami Mio / Nekomata Okayu / Inugami Korone
兎田ぺこら / 不知火フレア / 白銀ノエル / 宝鐘マリン
Usada Pekora / Shiranui Flare / Shirogane Noel / Houshou Marine
天音かなた / 角巻わため / 常闇トワ / 姫森ルーナ
Amane Kanata / Tsunomaki Watame / Tokoyami Towa / Himemori Luna
アユンダ・リス / ムーナ・ホシノヴァ / アイラニ・イオフィフティーン
Ayunda Risu / Moona Hoshinova / Airani Iofifteen
雪花ラミィ / 桃鈴ねね / 獅白ぼたん / 尾丸ポルカ
Yukihana Lamy / Momosuzu Nene / Shishiro Botan / Omaru Polka
森カリオペ / 小鳥遊キアラ / 一伊那尓栖 / がうる・ぐら
Mori Calliope / Takanashi Kiara / Ninomae Ina'nis / Gawr Gura
クレイジー・オリー / アーニャ・メルフィッサ / パヴォリア・レイネ
Kureiji Ollie / Anya Melfissa / Pavolia Reine
IRyS / セレス・ファウナ / オーロ・クロニー / 七詩ムメイ / ハコス・ベールズ
IRyS / Ceres Fauna / Ouro Kronii / Nanashi Mumei / Hakos Baelz
ラプラス・ダークネス / 鷹嶺ルイ / 博衣こより / 沙花叉クロヱ / 風真いろは
La+ Darknesss / Takane Lui / Hakui Koyori / Sakamata Chloe / Kazama Iroha
こぼ・かなえる / カエラ・コヴァルスキア / ベスティア・ゼータ
Kobo Kanaeru / Kaela Kovalskia / Vestia Zeta
シオリ・ノヴェラ / 古石ビジュー / ネリッサ・レイヴンクロフト / フワワ・アビスガード / モココ・アビスガード
Shiori Novella / Koseki Bijou / Nerissa Ravencroft / Fuwawa Abyssgard / Mococo Abyssgard
火威青 / 音乃瀬奏 / 一条莉々華 / 儒烏風亭らでん / 轟はじめ
Hiodoshi Ao / Otonose Kanade / Ichijou Ririka / Juufuutei Raden / Todoroki Hajime
hololive production COUNTDOWN LIVE 2024▷2025
Are you ready?
ライトに照らされて
In the spotlight
嘘と涙で笑えば
If I laugh with lies and tears
世にも美しき怪物
A beautiful monster in this world
女の子の出来上がり
A girl is complete
眉も目も唇も
Eyebrows, eyes, and lips
被写体向きの勝ち品
Winning pieces for the subject
暑い眼差しがなきゃ
Without a hot gaze
1000年の恋も冷めちゃうわ
Even a thousand-year love will cool
運命なんて生まれた日より
Fate is decided on the day you were born
選んだ服で決まるもの
By the clothes you chose
酸いも甘いも噛み締め
Savoring both sour and sweet
今をぎゅっとちゃんと愛して
Love the now tightly and properly
正面で見ても
Looking from the front
横から見ても
Looking from the side
下から見ても
Looking from below
いい女
A good woman
困っちゃう
It's a problem
君は全方向美少女
You are a beauty from all directions
困っちゃう
It's a problem
目元も背中も全部
Eyes and back, everything
愛として受け取るよ
I'll receive it as love
Eyes on you every time I find out you
You're the fire or ice or sweet sweet dream
You're music to my eyes and sweet sweet dream
アイライン完璧
Eyeliner is perfect
手間取ってるわまつげ
I'm taking time with my eyelashes
ほっぺに薔薇咲かせて
Make roses bloom on your cheeks
ルージュで誘い色つけて
Add inviting colors with rouge
よく人に好かれます
I'm often liked by people
魅せ方もわかってます
I know how to show myself off
毒も花も愛嬌も
Poison, flowers, and charm
常に腕に知恵を蓄えます
Always stock wisdom in your arms
幸福なんて一生かけて
Happiness is something you spend a lifetime
欲張って欲張って集めるもの
Greedily, greedily collecting
酸いも甘いも味わって
Taste both sour and sweet
今をぎゅっとちゃんと愛してね
Love the now tightly and properly
正面で見ても
Looking from the front
横から見ても
Looking from the side
下から見ても
Looking from below
いい女
A good woman
困っちゃう
It's a problem
君は全方向美少女
You are a beauty from all directions
困っちゃう
It's a problem
目元も背中も全部
Eyes and back, everything
愛として受け取るよ
I'll receive it as love
Eyes on you every time I find out you
You're the fire or ice or sweet sweet dream
君は全方向美少女
You are a beauty from all directions
チート、ギフト、All as I want it
Cheat, gift, All as I want it
禁忌、禁じ手、明らかにオーバー
Forbidden, foul play, clearly over
反則、異次元、この世のモンではないです
Foul, another dimension, not of this world
無理ゲー、それ聞いてないって
Impossible game, I didn't hear about that
Ah, ライバル口を揃えて
Ah, rivals all say in unison
バグで、マグで、認められてて
Recognized as a bug, as a mag
マジで？これをマジ全部生身で？
Seriously? All of this with just a physical body?
Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
It's 生身、It's 生身　Yeah Yeah Yeah
It's physical, it's physical Yeah Yeah Yeah
Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
実力を発揮し切る前に
Before showing my true strength
相手の方がバックれてくらしい
The opponent seems to run away
上がってるハードル Very Happy
The rising hurdle is Very Happy
明らかにダントツでピカイチ
Clearly the best by far
相変わらずガッピーしてる間に
While still gasping as usual
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
絶え間ない火光 もいらな もはやICUよりICY (Icy, icy)
Unending flashing lights, no longer needed, cooler than the ICU (Icy, icy)
俺 パッと見できない事ばかりだけど very happy
At a glance, there are many things I can't do, but I'm very happy
あきれてる あきれてる 周り 恵まれてる家族とダチ
Those around me are fed up, but I'm blessed with family and friends
反射的タッチ みんな俺に任せとけばいい
Reflexive touch, everyone can just leave it to me
一生ない紋章 一緒にない重宝 パッとのまじない
A crest that'll never exist, a treasure that's never together, a sudden spell
鏡よ鏡 答えちゃって Who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah
Mirror, mirror, answer me, who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah
生身のまま行けるトコまで To the next, to the 1番上
Going as far as I can in this flesh, to the next, to the very top
Now singin'
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
To the next, to the 1番上
To the next, to the very top
Eyday 俺のままで居るだけで超flex
Eyday, just being myself is a huge flex
Eyday 誰も口を挟ませない (Don't test)
Eyday, I won't let anyone interfere (Don't test)
Eyday 俺のままで居るだけで超flex
Eyday, just being myself is a huge flex
Eyday 誰も口を挟ませない (Don't test)
Eyday, I won't let anyone interfere (Don't test)
覚悟決める前科もねえ 余裕でBling-Bang-Bang
No criminal record before making a decision, effortlessly Bling-Bang-Bang
この存在自体が文化財なの最高位Bling-Bang-Bang
This existence itself is a cultural asset, the highest rank Bling-Bang-Bang
国境を超える目深ないアジアにBling-Bang-Bang
Crossing borders into the hidden Asia, Bling-Bang-Bang
動く各地揺らすEPこのレベルBling-Bang-Bang
Moving regions, shaking the EP, at this level Bling-Bang-Bang
パレットなら満杯完成のまわり 生身のことだんま
The palette is full, surrounding completion, keeping quiet about the raw truth
音楽幸 勝利の女神 今夜も散々ババンバ
Music luck, the goddess of victory, tonight as well, it's a wild party
漫画みたいな絵柄のままで 張り合いてしまってるワンガ
Staying in a manga-like style, competing with the wanderers
圧倒的力 この頭と口から
Overwhelming power, from this head and mouth
この体は吐いてない この空に刻みついてない
This body hasn't spat it out, it's not etched into this sky
繰り返しやらかすくたべちか いかつい年を刻みししわ
Repeating mistakes, a tough year etched in wrinkles
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
俺のままでBlingしてBangしてBornする為にBornして生きていこう
Born to Bling, Bang, and Born as myself, let's live on
鏡よ鏡 答えちゃって Who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah
Mirror, mirror, answer me, who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah
生身のまま行けるトコまで To the next, to the 1番上
Going as far as I can in this flesh, to the next, to the very top
Now singin'
Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang, Bling-Bang-Bang-Born
To the next, to the 1番上
To the next, to the very top
Eyday 俺のままで居るだけで超flex
Eyday, just being myself is a huge flex
Eyday 誰も口を挟ませない (Don't test)
Eyday, I won't let anyone interfere (Don't test)
Eyday 俺のままで居るだけで超flex
Eyday, just being myself is a huge flex
Eyday 誰も口を挟ませない (Don't test)
Eyday, I won't let anyone interfere (Don't test)
実際に感情はのせん 気づかないふり 絶対的な虚実と心中
In reality, I don't invest emotions, pretending not to notice, committing suicide with absolute falsehood
そうやって煽るアンチ 傷の切り売り 脆く叫ぶ醜態
Inciting antis like that, selling off my wounds, a fragile, screaming disgrace
そんなあなたにはお勧め 最高級の逃避行 やがて甘美な罠に嵌れば救われる
For someone like you, I recommend the finest escapism, if you eventually fall into the sweet trap, you'll be saved
もはや正気の沙汰ではやっていけないこの娑婆じゃ 敢えて差し出すその手に身を任せるのが最適解
You can no longer manage with sanity in this world, the best solution is to entrust yourself to that hand proactively offered
お言葉で飾った 寒空を 心を奪う甘い物だ
Decorated with words, the wintry sky is a sweet thing that steals your heart
全てが染まっていくような 辞書に交渉中
Negotiating with the dictionary as if everything is being dyed
さらば！ こんな事態にあつらえ 騙し騙されのギジャエエ 本能芝居で騙される
Farewell! Tailored for such a situation, a gigue of deceiving and being deceived, fooled by instinctive acting
やたらとうるさい心臓の音 正気はもう意味ないなんて 磨り減る耐久性
The heartbeats are incredibly noisy, sanity is no longer here, durability wearing thin
目の前の事象を傍受 現実に生きるの限界 お願い助けてね
Intercepting the phenomena before me, at the limit of living in reality, please help me
あなただんだん眠くなる 浅浅なメズマライズ 頭空っぽ無になれば もさかまた騙らか
You are getting sleepier and sleepier, a shallow mesmerization, if your head becomes empty and void, perhaps you'll be deceived again
目の前で揺らめく効果 動かなくなる体 これでいいんだ自分さえも 騙し騙しちゃった
The flickering effect before your eyes, a body that won't move, this is fine, I've even fooled myself
あなただんだん眠くなる 浅浅なメズマライズ...
You are getting sleepier and sleepier, a shallow mesmerization...
そんなに今日も意気抜いても 報われぬエブリデイ もうバカみたいなサイクルで だっさい瞬間を続けているの
Even if you exert yourself so much today, an unrewarding everyday, repeating useless moments in a foolish cycle
うまくいかないのはっぱ 恐ろしい情景 ないものねだり諦めて 余り物で勝負するのか
Things not going well is a terrible sight, give up on asking for the impossible, will you compete with leftovers?
さらば！ こんな事態にあつらえ 騙し騙されのギジャエエ 本能芝居で騙される
Farewell! Tailored for such a situation, a gigue of deceiving and being deceived, fooled by instinctive acting
やたらとうるさい心臓の音 正気はもう意味ないなんて 見せかけのカリスマ
The heartbeats are incredibly noisy, sanity is no longer here, a superficial charisma
現実を直視しすぎると 失明しちゃうんだ だから適当にね
If you look too closely at reality, you'll go blind, so just take it easy
はいよろこんで
Yes, with pleasure!
あなたがたのため
For your sake
はい謹んで
Yes, with respect
あなたがたのため
For your sake
忍び寄ってきたって
Even if it creeps up
その頃正義だって
Even if it was justice then
イェイイェイ生き延びて分かって
Yay yay, survive and understand
せーのであなたがた
Ready, set, you all
はいよろこんで
Yes, with pleasure!
あなたがたのために
For your sake
できることなら
If I can
できるところまで
As far as I can
あと一歩踏み出して
Take one more step forward
嫌なこと思い出して
Remembering the bad things
奈落を奏でろ
Play the abyss
ブンブンブン
Boom boom boom
もう一歩踏み出して
Take one more step forward
嫌なこと思い出して
Remembering the bad things
鳴らせ君の3から6まで
Ring your three to six
ギリギリダンス
On-the-edge dance
踊れ
Dance!
ギリギリダンス
On-the-edge dance
もっと鳴らせ
Ring it more!
鳴らせ君の病の街を
Ring your town of sickness
匿名笑える他人の Opinion
Anonymous laughable opinions of others
運転制御の超人たちを
The superhumans of driving control
鳴らせ君の3から6まで
Ring your three to six
ギリだとしても
Even if it's on the edge
優しさが勝つあなたの
Your kindness wins
欠けたとこが希望
The missing part is hope
Save this game, Mr. A.
救われたのは僕のうちのひとりで
One of me was saved
あと一歩踏み出して
Take one more step forward
嫌なこと思い出して
Remembering the bad things
奈落を奏でろ
Play the abyss
ブンブンブン
Boom boom boom
もう一歩踏み出して
Take one more step forward
嫌なこと思い出して
Remembering the bad things
鳴らせ君の3から6まで
Ring your three to six
開ける未知を無駄なの言葉済まして
Opening the unknown, ignoring words that it's useless
切り開く我儘の言葉
Carving out selfish words
高鳴る白生また新たな音は
The beating heart, yet again a new sound is...
ギリギリダンス
On-the-edge dance
踊れ
Dance!
ギリギリダンス
On-the-edge dance
もっと鳴らせ
Ring it more!
ギリギリダンス
On-the-edge dance
踊れ
Dance!
ギリギリダンス
On-the-edge dance
もっと鳴らせ
Ring it more!
鳴らせ君の病の街を
Ring your town of sickness
匿名笑える他人の Opinion
Anonymous laughable opinions of others
運転制御の超人たちを
The superhumans of driving control
鳴らせ君の3から6まで
Ring your three to six
はいよろこんで
Yes, with pleasure!
あなたがたのために
For your sake
できることなら
If I can
できるところまで
As far as I can
はい謹んで
Yes, with respect
あなたがたのために
For your sake
鳴らせ君の3から6まで
Ring your three to six
Hey boogie-woogie bam-bam
Let's go party-party boom-boom
Hu-wah! Hey you are my-my-my-my body
Be my body clap-clap-clap
With my body get up and down
Come on, choose-choose your body
And let's move-move your body
Let's enjoy and get closer day by day
Come on, choose-choose your body
And let's move-move your body
Let's enjoy and get even closer day by day
Happy smile face ha ha ha
It's me you my buddy-buddy
Woo-hoo! Party let's go! Boom-boom
Party-party enjoy happy!
シカのこのこのここしたんたん
Shikanoko nokonoko koshitantan
あらわるのこのこ
Emerging nonchalantly
ツナツナピョカピョカ
Antlers pitter-patter
見た目はおにゃの子
Looking like a girl
近頃うわさのなかなかきわもの
Lately a rumored quite eccentric thing
お手並みいかほどへなちょこ
Let's see your skills, you weakling
ずいぶん昔からジャパンに生息
Living in Japan since a long time ago
シカせんべいなら無下限ください
If it's deer crackers, give me an infinite amount
この界隈仲間カモシカウシカ
In this neighborhood, are they serows or cows?
でもでもまとめてぐーぜんもー
But but all together, it's just a coincidence
ルンロスパンステップでおどろー
Let's dance with run-ros-pan steps
夜が明けるまで 1, 2, 3
Until the dawn breaks, 1, 2, 3
何度だって反芻して ぬぬぬ
Ruminating over and over, nu nu nu
予測不可能シカ色で
Unpredictable in deer-colored style
アヴァンギャルドでおーらい
Avant-garde is all right
カオス増しまし
Chaos extra-large
いつの間にくせになって ぬぬぬ
Before I knew it, I was hooked, nu nu nu
あちゃめめちゃシカ色で
Oh my, very much in deer-colored style
アテコパチカモン
A-te-ko-pa-chi, come on
なんでもありルールなんてなし
Anything goes, there are no rules
キミの笑顔で元気満タン
Your smile fills me with energy
もしかして運命のマイアイディア
Maybe it's my destined idea
心のどこかで虎視眈々
Somewhere in my heart, waiting for the chance
キミとならいつまでも
Forever with you
シカのこのこのここしたんたん
Shikanoko nokonoko koshitantan
シカのここしがた
The deer's form
おだてりゃいちころ
One compliment and they're done
いやいや意外とつわものかもよ
No, no, they might be surprisingly tough
やることなすことドタバタ騒ぎで
Everything they do is a slapstick commotion
都合が歩けりゃテレポート
Teleporting if things are going well
ようこそシカ部へ集まりしシカ友
Welcome to the Deer Club, fellow deer friends
シカになりたけりゃ険しい道だぞ
If you want to be a deer, it's a steep path
いまどきJKなら時代はシカでしょ
If you're a modern JK, it's the era of the deer
シカせん片手にハイポーズ
Deer cracker in hand, strike a pose
みんなの声が響くよ
Everyone's voices are echoing
地球を超えて どこまでも
Beyond the Earth, wherever it may be
神の使い足るシカを崇めよ
Revere the deer, for they are messengers of God
シカの子神の子万々歳
Child of deer, child of God, hurray!
神の使い足るシカを崇めよ
Revere the deer, for they are messengers of God
シカの子神の子万々歳
Child of deer, child of God, hurray!
青春ってやつかもなんて
Maybe this is what they call youth
キラリキラリ輝いてるね
Sparkling and shining, isn't it?
眩しすぎるならグラスをはいどうぞ
If it's too bright, here, have some glasses
何度だって反芻して ぬぬぬ
Ruminating over and over, nu nu nu
予測不可能シカ色で
Unpredictable in deer-colored style
アヴァンギャルドでおーらい
Avant-garde is all right
カオス増しまし
Chaos extra-large
いつの間にくせになって ぬぬぬ
Before I knew it, I was hooked, nu nu nu
あちゃめめちゃシカ色で
Oh my, very much in deer-colored style
アテコパチカモン
A-te-ko-pa-chi, come on
なんでもありルールなんてなし
Anything goes, there are no rules
キミの笑顔で元気満タン
Your smile fills me with energy
もしもしかして運命のマイアイディア
Maybe it's my destined idea
心のどこかで虎視眈々
Somewhere in my heart, waiting for the chance
極秘：人類シカ化計画
Top Secret: Human Deer-ification Plan
そんなことはさせない！
I won't let that happen!
キミとならいつまでも
Forever with you
音が止まった
The sound stopped
色が変わった
The colors changed
空白だった
It was a blank
記憶の彼方
Beyond memories
ドラマみたいだ
It's like a drama
鼓動が鳴った
A heartbeat rang out
I wonder
足跡を辿って
Tracing the footprints
別れ道で立ち止まってる
Standing still at a fork in the road
八方美人で誤魔化した
Cheating with a facade that pleases everyone
きらめき 煙霧の向こう
A sparkle beyond the mist
本当のこと教えて
Tell me the truth
本当の自分に出会えた時
When I encountered my true self
愛し愛され未来が
A future of loving and being loved
きっと訪れる
Will surely come
見つめていたい
I want to keep watching
透明なまま素のキャンバス
The raw canvas remaining transparent
彩ったニュアンスカラーは
The shaded colors I painted
甘い甘い曖昧
Sweet, sweet ambiguity
探してた
I was looking for it
素直なままの君のパレット
Your palette, just as honest as it is
真実だけ描いてゆくから
Because I'll go on drawing only the truth
シャララララララララ
Sha-la-la-la-la-la-la-la
I wonder
重ねた色が涙で流れて
The layered colors are washed away by tears
虹色になるから
Because they'll become the colors of a rainbow
見つめていたい
I want to keep watching
透明なまま素のキャンバス
The raw canvas remaining transparent
...彩りだったニュアンスからは
...From the nuances that were once colors
淡い 甘い
Faint, sweet
探してた
I was searching
素直なままの君のパレットで
On your palette, just as you are
真実だけ描いていくから
Because I'll only paint the truth
音が止まった
The sound stopped
色が変わった
The colors changed
パズルみたいな
Like a puzzle
記憶の欠片
Fragments of memory
誰かが呼んだ
Someone called out
鼓動が鳴った
A heartbeat rang out
I wonder
もう一度さ　声を聞かせてよ
Let me hear your voice once more
めくれないままでいる　夏の日のカレンダー
A calendar from a summer day that remains unturned
「ただいま」ってさ　笑ってみせてよ
Say "I'm home" and show me a smile
送り先もわからない　忘れ物ばかりだ
I only have things left behind with no destination
心が壊れる音が聞こえて
Hearing the sound of my heart breaking
どれだけ君を愛していたか知って
Knowing just how much I loved you
もう二度とは増やせない
I can't add any more
思い出を抱いて生きて
I'll live on holding our memories
デイバイデイ
Day by day
どんなスピードで追いかけたら
At what speed must I chase
また君と巡り逢えるだろう
To be able to meet you again?
寄り添った日々に生きている意味
The meaning of living in the days we stood together
くれたのは君なんだよ
Was given to me by you
だから
So
いつも心で想い続けてる
I'm always thinking of you in my heart
まだ僕の声は聞こえてる？
Can you still hear my voice?
止まらない日々　君に会う度
The days that don't stop, every time I see you
よく似合う笑み浮かべて待ってて
Wait for me with that smile that suits you so well
言えなかった胸の奥の言葉
The words deep in my chest I couldn't say
今ならありのまま君に渡せる
Now I can give them to you just as they are
囁き合った　おどけられたより
Rather than whispering or joking around
0センチの指先で　渡せた君なでてた
With my fingertips at 0cm, I was stroking you
どうしてかな　離れている方が
I wonder why, when we are apart
言葉溢れ出すのは　今さらと笑って
Words overflow; laughing that it's too late now
君だけ見つけた　いつかの流星
A meteor that only you found back then
どんな願いを浮かべていたのかな
I wonder what kind of wish you were thinking of
あの日君が見上げてた
On that day you were looking up
藍色の先を見つめて
Staring beyond the indigo
デイバイデイ
Day by day
幾億光年の距離を越えて
Crossing the distance of billions of light years
輝きを伝う星のように
Like a star transmitting its radiance
変わらない愛　確かな光
An unchanging love, a steady light
届くまで願い続ける
I'll keep wishing until it reaches you
だから
So
いつか僕ら巡り逢えたなら
If we can meet again someday
輝きの中で待ち合わせよう
Let's meet within the radiance
君が迷子にならないように
So that you won't get lost
瞬きもせず　照らして待ってる
I'll wait, shining without even blinking
消えやしない　君がくれた温もり
The warmth you gave me will never fade
抱きしめ僕は今を生きていくから
Embracing it, I will live in the present
名前を呼ぶよ
I'll call your name
来る日も来る日も
Day after day
絶えず叫ぶよ
I'll scream it out incessantly
あのままの二人でいようよ
Let's stay the two of us just like that
デイバイデイ
Day by day
どんなスピードで追いかけたら
At what speed must I chase
また君と巡り逢えるだろう
To be able to meet you again?
分かち合った日々　季節は不意に
The days we shared; the seasons suddenly
君だけを乗せ彼方へ
Carrying only you far away
だから
So
いつまでも心で想い続けてる まだ僕の声は聞こえてる？
I'll keep thinking of you in my heart forever, can you still hear my voice?
包み出し日々 目を開けるたび
In the days that unfold, every time I open my eyes,
近づいていく 運命と真実へ
I'm drawing closer to destiny and truth.
言えなかった 胸の奥の言葉
The words deep in my heart that I couldn't say,
今ならありのまま君に渡せる
I can give them to you just as they are now.
どれだけの時が流れても
No matter how much time passes,
永遠に過去形にならない I love you
My 'I love you' will never be in the past tense.
さよーならまたいつか！
Goodbye, until we meet again someday!
どこから春が巡り来るのか
From where does the spring come around?
知らず知らず大人になった
Before I knew it, I had become an adult.
見上げた先にツバメが飛んでいた けのなき顔で
Looking up, a swallow was flying with an indifferent face.
もしも私に翼があれば
If I had wings,
長い旅に悲しみ暮らと
I'd spend a long journey in sadness.
さよなら100年先でまた会いましょう
Goodbye, let's meet again in a hundred years.
心配しないで
Don't you worry.
いつの間にか花が落ちた
Before I knew it, the flowers had fallen.
誰かが私に嘘をついた
Someone told me a lie.
土砂降りでも構わず飛んでいく
Flying off regardless of the downpour,
その力が欲しかった
I wanted that kind of strength.
誰かと恋に落ちて また砕けて
Falling in love with someone, then breaking again,
やがて離れ離れ
And eventually drifting apart.
口の中は血が滲んで
With blood seeping in my mouth,
空に唾を吐く
I spit at the sky.
瞬け羽を広げ
Twinkle and spread your wings,
気ままに飛べ
Fly as you please,
どこまでも行け
Go as far as you can.
100年先も覚えてるかな
I wonder if I'll remember in a hundred years.
知らねえけれど さよならまたいつか
I don't know, but goodbye until we meet again.
しぐるるやしぐるる街あゆみ入る
Walking into the drizzling, drizzling town,
そこかしこで袖触れる
Brushing sleeves here and there.
見えてた先に何もいなかった
There was nothing at the destination I saw,
ああ いなかった
Oh, there was nothing.
したり顔で触らないで
Don't touch me with that smug look,
背中を殴りつける窓外れ
Hitting my back, missing the window.
人ゴミの友 地獄の先にこそ
Friend in the crowd, it's beyond the hell
私は春を見る
That I see the spring.
誰かを愛したくて でも痛くて
Wanting to love someone, but it hurts,
いつしか雨上がれ
May the rain stop someday.
繋がっていた縄を握りしめて
Clutching the rope that held us together,
死ぬかと道ちぎる
I tear through the path as if I might die.
貫け狙い定め
Pierce through, take your aim,
蹴散らし捕らえ
Scatter them and capture,
どこまでも行け
Go as far as you can.
100年先のあなたに会いたい
I want to see you in a hundred years.
消え失せるなよ さよならまたいつか
Don't you fade away, goodbye until we meet again.
今 恋に落ちて また砕けて
Now falling in love, then breaking again,
離れ離れ
Drifting apart.
口の中は血が滲んで
With blood seeping in my mouth,
空に唾を吐く
I spit at the sky.
今 羽を広げ
Now spread your wings,
気ままに飛べ
Fly as you please,
どこまでも行け
Go as far as you can.
生まれた日から私知ってたんだ
I've known it since the day I was born.
知らなかっただろ さよならまたいつか
You didn't know, did you? Goodbye until we meet again.
晩餐歌
Bansanka
君を泣かすから だから一緒にはいれないな
Because I'll make you cry, that's why we can't be together.
君を泣かすから 早く忘れてほしいんだ
Because I'll make you cry, I want you to forget me soon.
人間だからね たまには違うものも食べたいね
We're only human, so sometimes we want to eat something different.
君を泣かすから そう君を泣かすから
Because I'll make you cry, yes, because I'll make you cry.
でも 味気ないないないだよね 会いたい会いたくないんだよね
But it's so bland, isn't it? You want to see me, yet you don't.
君が会いたい会いたくないんだよね なんて勝手だね
You want to see me, yet you don't. How selfish of you.
大体曖昧なんだよね
It's usually vague, isn't it?
愛の存在証明なんて
Proof of love's existence and all.
君が教えて
Won't you teach me
くれないか
about it?
何十回の夜を過ごしたって
Even after spending dozens of nights,
得られぬような愛してるを
the 'I love you's' I can't seem to get—
並べてみて
try lining them up.
何十回の夜を過ごしたって
Even after spending dozens of nights,
得られぬような最高の
give me the ultimate
フルコースを頂戴
full course meal.
君を退かすから
Since I'll push you away,
きっと一生は無理だよね
it'll surely be impossible for a lifetime.
君を退かすから
Since I'll push you away,
胸がとても痛むんだ
my heart hurts so much.
人間だからね
Since we're only human,
たまには分かり合えなくなって
we sometimes stop understanding each other.
君を退かすから
Since I'll push you away,
また君を退かすから
since I'll push you away again.
でも自信がないないないんだよね
But I have no confidence, none at all,
変わりたくないないないんだよね
and I don't want to change, not at all.
君が愛おしくないんだよね
I don't find you precious,
なんて勝手だね
how selfish of me.
大体曖昧だったよね
It was usually vague, wasn't it?
愛の存在証明なんて
Proof of love's existence and all.
君がそこにいるのにね
Even though you're right there.
何百回の夜を過ごしたって
Even after spending hundreds of nights,
得られぬような愛してるを
the 'I love you's' I can't seem to get—
並べてみて
try lining them up.
何百回の夜を過ごしたって
Even after spending hundreds of nights,
得られぬような最高の
give me the ultimate
フルコースを頂戴
full course meal.
離れないでそばにいて
The one who stayed
くれたのは
by my side and never left,
結局君一人だったよね
in the end, was only you.
涙もスパイスは
Even the spice of tears is
君の物真似に
for your imitation,
残ってしまうだろうけど
though it'll probably remain.
何千回の夜を過ごしたって
Even after spending thousands of nights,
得られぬような愛してるを
the 'I love you's' I can't seem to get—
並べるから
I'll line them up.
何千回の夜を過ごしたって
Even after spending thousands of nights,
得られぬような最高の
give me the ultimate
フルコースを頂戴
full course meal.
何万回の夜を過ごしたって
Even after spending tens of thousands of nights,
忘れぬような愛してるを
the 'I love you's' I won't ever forget—
並べるから
I'll line them up.
何万回の夜を過ごしたって
Even after spending tens of thousands of nights,
忘れぬような最高の
give me the ultimate
フルコースを頂戴
full course meal.
晴る / 晴る / 作詞・作曲：n-buna
Sunny / Sunny / Lyrics & Composition: n-buna
貴方は風のように 目を閉じては夕暮れ
Like the wind, you close your eyes in the twilight.
何を思っているんだろうか
I wonder what you are thinking about.
瞼を開いていた 貴方の目はビードロ
Your eyes were open, like glass beads.
少しだけ晴るの匂いがした
They smelled a little bit like the sunny sky.
晴れに晴れ、花よ咲け
Clear up, oh sunny sky, let the flowers bloom.
咲いて晴るのせい
Bloom, it's all thanks to the sunny sky.
降り止まぬ雨でさえ
Even the rain that never stops falling,
貴方を飾る晴る
it's the sunshine that adorns you.
胸を打つ音よ鳴れ
Sound out, the beat within my chest.
鳴いて晴る風
Cry out, sunny breeze.
貴方まで凍えて逝け
Go on and freeze, even you,
遠くまだ遠くまで
far away, further still.
貴方は晴れ模様に 目を閉じては頬色
In the clear weather, you close your eyes with flushed cheeks.
何か悲しいのだろうか
I wonder if something is making you sad.
晴る
Haru
まぶたを開いている
Opening my eyelids
あなたの目にビトロ
Vitro in your eyes
今、少し雨の匂い
Now, a slight scent of rain
明日、
Tomorrow,
晴れに晴れ、空よ裂け
Clear and clear, oh sky, tear open
去勢、雨の精
Subdue, spirits of rain
降り頻く土砂雨さえ
Even the pouring downpour
雲の上では晴る
Is clear above the clouds
土を穿つ音よ鳴れ
Sound that pierces the earth, ring out
亡ら晴らへ
To the distant clear sky
あの雲も超えていく
Crossing even those clouds
遠く、まだ遠くまで
Farther, still farther away
鳥、雨、草を靡かせ
Bird, rain, making the grass sway
羊雲、あれも春の精
Altocumulus clouds, they too are spirits of spring
風のよう、胸に張るの精
Like the wind, a spirit swelling in my heart
春を待つ
Waiting for spring
晴れに晴れ、空よ裂け
Clear and clear, oh sky, tear open
去勢、雨の精
Subdue, spirits of rain
降り止まぬ雨でさえ
Even the rain that won't stop
あなたを飾る晴る
Is the clearing that adorns you
胸を穿つ音奏で
Playing the sound that pierces the chest
亡ら晴る風
The wind that clears away
音に聞く晴るの方
The way of the clearing I hear
さあこの歌よ投げ
Now, throw this song
晴れに晴れ、花よ咲け
Clear and clear, oh flowers, bloom
去勢、雨の精
Subdue, spirits of rain
あの雲も超えていく
Crossing even those clouds
遠く、まだ遠くまで
Farther, still farther away
2024.11.18
鬼ノ宴
Oni no Utage
どこから食えば良いものか
Where should I start eating from?
美味いものか 不味いものか
Is it tasty? Is it nasty?
さっぱり俺にゃ分からない
I have no clue at all
決まりばかりの世の中じゃ
In a world full of nothing but rules
仏がいつも道を指す
The Buddha is always pointing the way
伽藍、空ろが礼、偽者
Empty temples bowing, an impostor
鬼がこの身を唆す
An ogre tempts this body
お先にどうぞ、遠慮なく
Go ahead before me, don't be shy
赤ら開けやそのお口
Open that mouth of yours wide
宴、宴が始まんで
The feast, the feast is starting
勿体ねえや一度きり
What a waste, it's only once
好きなものだけ食べなはれ
Just eat whatever you like
あ、どっちをめくりゃ良いものか
Ah, which one should I flip over?
白い札か黒い札か
The white card or the black card?
一丁賭けるとしましょうか
Shall we place a bet?
死ぬも生きるも紙一重
Life and death are but a paper's breadth apart
お釈迦が蜘蛛の糸たらす
The Buddha dangles a spider's thread
遅くはないわ、おいでなさい
It's not too late, come along
地獄の声が耳を打つ
The voices of hell beat against my ears
踏み外すのも悪くない
Losing one's footing isn't so bad either
甘さかりやこの宴
This feast of overflowing sweetness
今宵、今宵は返さねえ
Tonight, tonight I won't let you go back
えもたけなわ、あかよろし
At the peak of the night, everything is fine
落ちる どこまで 落ちなはれ
Falling, how far will you fall?
回れ回れや 開け開けや
Spin, spin around, open, open up
回れ回れや 開けや
Spin, spin around, open up
回れ回れや 開け開けや
Spin, spin around, open, open up
回れ回れや 開けや
Spin, spin around, open up
赤火が消えそう その口
The red light's about to fade, that mouth
宴、宴が始まって
The banquet, the banquet has begun
もったいねえや 一度きり 好きなものだけ 食べなはれ
It's a waste, just this once, eat only what you like
落ちる どこまで
Falling, how far
落ちなはれ
Will you fall?
微睡みから覚める 濡れた瞼を蹴る
Waking from a slumber, kicking my wet eyelids
狂おしいほど脆いコースと追い求めるサウダージ
A path so fragile it's maddening, and the saudade I pursue
身を焼かれるような 絶望も糧になろうか
Could even a despair that burns my body become my sustenance?
憧れに焦がれるまま燃やし続けている
Yearning for my aspirations, I continue to burn
ギラギラ欲しさまよい堕ちたあんたの愛
Glistening with desire, your love that wandered and fell
空から乾いた可哀そうなロックスター
A pitiful rockstar, parched and dry
すべてを孤独から眩しい光
Everything from solitude, a dazzling light
僕にだけ落ちる影は あなたのせい
The shadow that falls only on me is because of you
致命的な結末をくれたね 気味勝手な個性 狂わされたせい
You gave me a fatal ending, didn't you? A selfish personality, driven mad by it
お願い 声を聞かせて
Please, let me hear your voice
声を聞かせて
Let me hear your voice
絡まって歪んでしまった傷さえ
Even the wounds that have become entangled and distorted
触れられるのはあなただけ
The only one who can touch them is you
あなただけ ああ
Only you, ah
あなただけ
Only you
お願い 僕を見ていて
Please, keep looking at me
僕を見ていて
Keep looking at me
宿命に刻まれた痛みさえ武器にして
Turning even the pain carved into my destiny into a weapon
いつかの後悔
So that I can scream out
叫び出せるように
My future regrets
あなたがいないと生きていけない
I can't live without you
何もかも捧げてしまってもいい
I don't mind sacrificing everything
あなたの愛がまだ足りない
Your love is still not enough
欠けたものは何で埋めたらいい
What should I fill the missing pieces with?
致命的、致命的、致命的な愛
Fatal, fatal, fatal love
埋めて、埋めて、埋めていく愛
Filling, filling, filling love
必然的、必然的、必然的な愛
Inevitable, inevitable, inevitable love
僕を見ていてね 最愛のファタール
Keep looking at me, my dearest fatale
ギラギラ欲しさまよい堕ちたあんたの愛
Glistening with desire, your love that wandered and fell
心から乾いた可哀そうなロックスター
A pitiful rockstar, parched from the heart
絡み合うダカラ あなただけ 美しさに
Entwining, therefore only you, in beauty
焼かれた目
Burned eyes
もがれた羽 想像的だって
Torn wings, even if it's imaginative
甘い視界をジャッジ その輝きはエゴイスティック
Judging the sweet vision, that brilliance is egoistic
胸の奥底 感情さえ 引っ張り出して昇華して
Even the feelings deep in my chest, pull them out and sublimate them
僕という運命を 全部抱きしめてゆく
Embracing all of the destiny that is me
あなたがいないと生きていけない
I can't live without you
眩しさでこの身を照らしてほしい
I want you to shine your brilliance upon me
あなたの愛がまだ足りない
Your love is still not enough
夢の中へもらうしかないのに
Even though I can only receive it in my dreams
致命的、致命的、致命的な愛
Fatal, fatal, fatal love
埋めて、埋めて、埋めていく愛
Filling, filling, filling love
必然的、必然的、必然的な愛
Inevitable, inevitable, inevitable love
誰のものでもない 最愛 of ファタール
Belonging to no one else, my dearest fatale
何度悔やんだだろう
How many times have I regretted?
何度呪っただろう
How many times have I cursed?
どれほど不幸を注いだとしても 満たされることのない器
No matter how much misfortune I pour in, it's a vessel that can never be filled
何度夢見たろう
How many times have I dreamed?
何度願っただろう
How many times have I wished?
僕の胸で 膿み続けてる傷
The wound that continues to fester in my chest
撫でる手を
The stroking hand
この舞台で足掻くことをやめない
I won't stop struggling on this stage
ただ一つの愛に近づきたい
I just want to get closer to one love
固く定まったこの宿命
This firmly fixed destiny
あの星の光から零れた闇
The darkness that spilled from the light of that star
あなたがいないと生きていけない
I can't live without you
何もかも捧げてしまってもいい
I don't mind sacrificing everything
あなたの愛がまだ足りない
Your love is still not enough
欠けたものは何で埋めたらいい
What should I fill the missing pieces with?
致命的、致命的、致命的な愛
Fatal, fatal, fatal love
埋めて、埋めて、埋めていく愛
Filling, filling, filling love
必然的、必然力、必然的な愛
Inevitable, inevitable, inevitable love
僕を見ていてね 最愛のファタール
Keep looking at me, my dearest fatale
最愛のファタール
My dearest fatale
ゆ　どったきどりでてん
You, pretending to have done it.
イガク
作詞・作曲：原口沙輔
Igaku
Lyrics/Composition: Sasuke Haraguchi
愛　爆ぜてろ
Love, go explode.
散漫になれば
If you get distracted.
う　まってまってまって
U- wait, wait, wait.
ゆ　どったきどりです
You, pretending to have done it.
相　そいかも
Maybe compatible.
もろとも
Together.
う　めてめてめて
U- bury, bury, bury.
ゆ　どこにもないから寝ていたら
It's nowhere, so while I was sleeping...
壊れて泣いてる夢を見たんだよ
...I had a dream of breaking and crying.
直に　庭　嘘に見えてくる
Soon, even the garden looks like a lie.
ゆ　顔が鈍器になっちゃうよ
Your face is gonna become a blunt weapon.
偽が現を獲ったんだ
The fake has taken over reality.
ゆ　無くなってほしいもののが
The things you want gone...
どうやら生き延びてしまった
...seem to have survived somehow.
生き延びてしまったんだ
They've survived somehow.
足が手枷になっちゃうよ
Your feet are gonna become shackles.
嘘が動悸になったんだ
The lies have become heart palpitations.
ゆ　疑ってほしいほどのあ
So much that I want you to doubt it...
どうやら方針だと思った
...it seems I thought it was a plan.
方針だと思ったんだ
I thought it was a plan.
無情
Heartless.
ゆ　どったきどりです
You, pretending to have done it.
全部やめろよ
Stop everything.
アティチュード
Attitude.
感動に届くもど
Reaching for emotion.
どんとこのどくのほうだけ
Only towards the poison.
わった　わった　わった
Watta watta watta.
顔が鈍器になっちゃうよ
Your face is gonna become a blunt weapon.
偽が現を獲ったんだ
The fake has taken over reality.
ゆ　無くなってほしいもののが
The things you want gone...
どうやら生き延びてしまった
...seem to have survived somehow.
生き延びてしまったんだ
They've survived somehow.
音が火野になってしま
The sound becomes a field of fire...
人が偽りに集ま
People gather around lies.
ふさがってしまいよ耳耳
My ears are getting blocked up.
どうやら波みたい
It seems like waves.
届いてないみたいね
It seems they haven't reached.
無情
Heartless.
純情何それ愛状何それ
Pure heart? What's that? Love? What's that?
美味しいのめ美味しいのってね
Is it tasty? Is it tasty?
乱暴だめだめ感情捨て去り
Violence is bad, cast away your feelings.
いっせーのでぶっ飛ぶだけ
All together now, just fly away.
混沌ブギウギハッピーで
Chaos boogie-woogie and happy.
毒盛りどんびいちゃいだ
Poisoned and weirded out.
どんびいちゃいだも
Weirded out indeed.
だんだん落ちてくIQ
My IQ is dropping steadily.
糞ワロいっせーので
LOL, all together now.
死ぬまで踊れ
Dance until you die.
混沌ブギ
作詞・作曲：Jon-YAKITORY
Chaos Boogie
Lyrics/Composition: Jon-YAKITORY
完全体の山田
The perfect form of Yamada.
無関心なんてあり得ない
Indifference is simply impossible.
三千体の桑田
Three thousand forms of Kuwata.
の方がいいかな
Would be better, maybe?
わがままばかりじゃ落ち着かない
Can't settle down if I'm just being selfish.
冷や汗が出過ぎて気持ち悪い
Too much cold sweat, I feel sick.
当たり前のことも手に付かない
Can't even do the obvious things.
もうなんて言えばいいばかりで
I'm just full of "what should I say?".
世間体とか投げ出したい
I want to throw away social appearances.
狂ったように泣き出したい
I want to start crying like crazy.
お望みがまま生きて消えていきたいな
I want to live as I please and then fade away.
純情何それ愛状何それ
Pure heart? What's that? Love? What's that?
美味しいのめ美味しいのってね
Is it tasty? Is it tasty?
乱暴だめだめ感情捨て去り
Violence is bad, cast away your feelings.
いっせーのでぶっ飛ぶだけ
All together now, just fly away.
混沌ブギウギハッピーで
Chaos boogie-woogie and happy.
毒盛りどんびいちゃいだ
Poisoned and weirded out.
どんびいちゃいだも
Weirded out indeed.
だんだん落ちてくIQ
My IQ is dropping steadily.
糞ワロいっせーので
LOL, all together now.
死ぬまで踊れ
Dance until you die.
1、2のまさかの3、4、5
1, 2, and then a surprising 3, 4, 5.
かりとりもういいんだってもういいんだって
Harvested, it's enough already, enough.
パンピーお代わりギミー時めき
Normies, seconds please, give me excitement.
いっせーのでさあ飛び込め
All together now, come on, jump in.
混沌ブギウギ簡単楽盛り
Chaos boogie-woogie, simple and fun.
もういいんだってもういいんだって
Enough already, enough.
最低奴らのライカ見捨てり
Abandoning the Leica of those lowlifes.
いっせーのでぶっ飛ぶだけ
All together now, just fly away.
混沌ブギウギハッピーで
Chaos boogie-woogie and happy.
毒盛りどんびいちゃいだ
Poisoned and weirded out.
どんびいちゃいだも
Weirded out indeed.
だんだん落ちてく人生
My life is dropping steadily.
糞ワロいっせーので
LOL, all together now.
死ぬまで踊れ
Dance until you die.
もういいや全部ほら
That's enough of everything, look.
忘れてしまおう
Let's just forget it all.
簡単なことじゃないか
Isn't it simple?
我々ならできるだろう
If it's us, we can do it.
あーーーーー！
Aaaaaah!
花になって
Becoming a Flower
いい加減にそっと隠れようがいいんじゃない
Why not just hide away quietly for once?
蕾のような花だってあるんじゃない
There must be flowers that stay as buds, right?
秘密にして守るのがいいんじゃない
Isn't it better to keep it a secret and protect it?
誰にも邪魔されず華麗に咲いている
Blooming magnificently, undisturbed by anyone.
甘い苦いにハマらない
I won't get caught up in sweet or bitter.
その判断が下らない
That judgment is worthless.
気に病む暇を浮かさないでいて
Don't let even a moment of worry surface.
愛になりきれない
I can't fully become love.
無駄に飾らない
I won't decorate in vain.
綺麗にされた花瓶も 肥やしも何もいらない
I don't need fancy vases, fertilizer, or anything.
その姿が美しい
That appearance itself is beautiful.
花になって ほらニヒルに笑って その香りに
Become a flower, see, laugh nihilistically, and with that scent...
ゾクゾクして目が離せない
It makes me shiver, I can't look away.
味にして 君の毒は私の薬
Savoring it, your poison is my medicine.
纏う化けの皮 笑って
Wearing this disguise, just laugh.
ねぇ 痛い痛い痛い その笑顔に
Hey, it hurts, hurts, hurts, seeing that smile...
痛い痛い痛い 永遠を笑ってくれるかな
It hurts, hurts, hurts... will you laugh with me for eternity?
影から支えるくらいがいいんじゃない
Isn't it fine just supporting from the shadows?
欲を言えばこの手で咲かせて見せたい
If I'm being greedy, I want to make you bloom with my own hands.
病のように 心を喰らう花
A flower that devours the heart like a disease.
枯らしたくないのさ
I don't want it to wither.
光が届かずとも 水をあげ続けるから
Even if light doesn't reach, I'll keep giving it water.
いい加減に気づいて 君は素敵すぎて
Won't you realize already? You're just too wonderful.
惚れ惚れもっとお大事に
I'm fascinated; please take better care of yourself.
無自覚のまま愛を蓄えて
Storing up love without even realizing it.
綺麗にされた花瓶も 肥やしも何もいらない
I don't need fancy vases, fertilizer, or anything.
その姿で咲き誇れ
In that form, bloom in full glory.
花になって ほらニヒルに笑って その香りに
Become a flower, see, laugh nihilistically, and with that scent...
ゾクゾクして目が離せない
It makes me shiver, I can't look away.
味にして 君の毒は私の薬
Savoring it, your poison is my medicine.
纏う化けの皮
Wearing this disguise.
逆にして 君の闇は私の光
Conversely, your darkness is my light.
愛し長けたら 笑って
If love thrives, then laugh.
ここからは、ホロライブオリジナル曲パートです！盛り上がっていくぞー！
From here on, it's the Hololive original songs part! Let's get hyped!
ビビデバ
Bibideba
つまんないデコボコ勘定 素敵願ってるだけの人生
Dull, uneven calculations, a life spent just wishing for something wonderful.
Wait a minute ズルズルヘッジホッグ トリックなしの毎日
Wait a minute, dragging on like a hedgehog, days without any tricks.
I wanna be free だってマジなプレッシャー してパーティーはスタートさ
I wanna be free, 'cause it's serious pressure, then let the party start.
Hey 待って ちょっと待って
Hey wait, wait a second.
良心は躍らせて 夜を急かす 魔法のよう
Let your conscience dance, rushing through the night like magic.
人生は一瞬に沈めて 溶ける魔法
Submerge life in an instant, a magic that dissolves.
それならば駆け抜けて 舞い踊り
In that case, run through and dance your heart out.
お邪魔な馬車を飛び乗って タイムリー 私も大変身メーカー
Hopping on that troublesome carriage, timely, I'm a transformation maker too.
わがままのまにまにきらめき 満ち満ち
Sparkling at the mercy of selfishness, overflowing with light.
Shut upな街で ダンシング さよなら グッバイ レッツゴー
Dancing in the 'shut up' town, farewell, goodbye, let's go.
It's a 喝采 クラップ 踊り出す 皆見逃すな 浴びあそばせ
It's an applause, clap, start to dance, don't miss it, everyone, soak it in.
ビビデバビデブーは ビビデバビデブーは Yeah
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo is... Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo is... Yeah!
こんがらがっちゃってもしょうがない 華麗にステップさ
It's okay to get all tangled up, just step magnificently.
...tonight
ビビデバビデブーワ　ビビデバビデブーワ yeah
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wa Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wa, yeah
今夜に明日はないなら　12時に怒涛門勝ちでしょ
If there's no tomorrow for tonight, it's a landslide victory at 12 o'clock, right?
ただ済まれよほ　どんな問題も解法一つ
Just be done with it, ho. Every problem has one solution.
拍手も正解も間違いも　愛す本当の私の気障
Applause, correct answers, and mistakes—I love them all, the real, affected me.
あれ何だか正解は限界の　気配がして
Wait, I feel like the correct answer is reaching its limit.
当てられたら安心じゃ心配
If it hits the mark, it's a worry rather than a relief.
Ay 今すぐ jumping jumping out
Ay, jumping jumping out right now.
チキチキバンバン　チキチキバンバン
Chiki chiki bang bang, chiki chiki bang bang.
威場抱くに危機享楽日々に
Holding onto prestige in these days of peril and pleasure.
ギリギリバンバン　弾けみたい大砲
Giri giri bang bang, like a cannon about to burst.
発射してしまおうか
Shall we fire it off?
まだまだビビらんなくミニバンシャー
I'm not scared yet, I'm a mini adventurer.
一発じゃ足りないわ
One shot isn't enough.
次に導き出した君にアンサー
The next answer I derive is for you.
灰になるまで踊ってよう
Let's dance until we turn to ash.
ビビデバビデブーワ　ビビデバビデブーワ yeah
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wa Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wa, yeah
おしゃまらばしちゃうヴィーナス Driving
A precocious Venus driving.
私は大変身メイクアップ　わがままの...
I'm making a major transformation, makeup, selfish...
Shut up the mouth です　ガツンとサヨナラ
Shut your mouth. A blunt goodbye.
Goodbye 統合だ　いつかは喝采食らう
Goodbye to integration. Someday, I'll receive applause.
ウォーリアーズ皆々ご唱和あれ
Warriors, everyone, sing along.
ビビデバビデブーワ　ビビデバビデブーワ yeah
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wa Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wa, yeah
こんがらがっちゃってもしょうがないから　シューズと繋い
It can't be helped if it gets tangled, so connect with your shoes.
ビビデバビデブーワ　ビビデバビデブーワ yeah
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wa Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wa, yeah
今夜に明日はないなら　12時に怒涛門勝ちでしょ
If there's no tomorrow for tonight, it's a landslide victory at 12 o'clock, right?
5、4、3、2、1、0！
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 0!
Happy New Year!!
Happy New Year!
あけましておめでとうございます！
今年もよろしくお願いします！
I look forward to working with you again this year!
新年一発目は...
The first one of the new year is...
瞬間ハートビート！
Momentary Heartbeat!
Happy New Year! あけましておめでとう！
Happy New Year! Happy New Year!
ReGLOSS と bu-ia-ra
ReGLOSS and we are
Regloss!
新年一発目は...
The first one of the new year is...
瞬間ハートビート！
Momentary Heartbeat!
今年もよろしくね！ yeah！
Happy new year! yeah!
漠然とした不安　欲していた分
The vague anxiety and the minutes I spent
日常に違和感　うんざりしていた
The discomfort in daily life, I was fed up with it
見慣れた景色　足りない眺め
A familiar view, an insufficient sight
理屈を越える変化を求めていた
I was seeking a change that defies logic
窮屈で退屈な日々の中
In these cramped and boring days
突然君は現れた
Suddenly, you appeared
全身の細胞　駆け巡るように
Like it's racing through every cell in my body
走り出した未完成なストーリー
An incomplete story has started running
モノクロだった景色が今
The landscape that was monochrome is now...
君と出会えばカラフルに彩る ban-new world
...becoming a brand new world, colored brightly by meeting you
心奪われた気まぐれな瞬間ハートビート
My heart was stolen by this whimsical, momentary heartbeat
揺ら軸の狭間もう一人じゃない煌めく星
In the gap of the fluctuating axis, I'm no longer alone, a twinkling star
描く未来予想図は同じ夢を引き寄せたいよ
I want the future blueprint I draw to pull in the same dream
果てしない旅路の向こうで鳴り止まない浪漫が待っている
Beyond the endless journey, a never-ending romance awaits
気付いた時にはね I can't live without you
By the time I noticed, I can't live without you
いつまでも君と一緒にいなら
If I'm with you forever...
これから先広がる宇宙
...the universe will expand from here on
晴れ渡った空飛び出して気分は上昇想像以上
Flying out into the clear sky, my mood is rising beyond imagination
机上の空論は終わりにして全て叶える空言
Putting an end to idle talk, making all the impossible dreams come true
時計の針が回り回る
The hands of the clock turn round and round
限りない時の中で鮮やかにダンシングタイム
In the infinite time, a vivid dancing time
心奪われた気まぐれな瞬間ハートビート
My heart was stolen by this whimsical, momentary heartbeat
揺ら軸の狭間もう一人じゃない煌めく星
In the gap of the fluctuating axis, I'm no longer alone, a twinkling star
描く未来予想図は同じ夢を引き寄せたいよ
I want the future blueprint I draw to pull in the same dream
果てしない旅路の向こうに鳴り止まない浪漫が待っている
Beyond the endless journey, a never-ending romance awaits
奇跡があるはず
There must be a miracle.
さよならメランコリー
Goodbye melancholy.
止められはしない この衝動と
This impulse won't be stopped.
突き進むだけさ 何振り構わず
Just keep pushing forward, no matter what.
Are you ready?
限界はないさ 純度無限大の1次元
There are no limits, a 1st dimension of infinite purity.
散りばめた煌めき 夜空見上げて
Looking up at the night sky, filled with scattered sparkles.
喜びは悲しみの倍 分かち合っていこう
Joy is double the sorrow, let's share it together.
君とならどこまでも
With you, anywhere.
2025年も、ReGLOSSよろしくね！
Please support ReGLOSS in 2025 too!
波打ち際 解けた髪 帽子の先
By the water's edge, hair undone, the tip of my hat.
身に覚えある 蒼い輪郭
A familiar blue silhouette,
Stop the flashback
南風の
The south wind's...
いたずらな魔法
...playful magic.
It's magic red
夏のあの目眩に 戻さないで
Don't let me go back to that summer dizziness.
秘密を あげた
I gave you a secret.
Maybe love stray my heart
何食わぬ 顔をして キスを
With an innocent face, a kiss...
奪って 遠くへ
...taken far away.
今だけは 寄り添ってあげるわ
Just for now, I'll stay close to you.
唇に 温もり 残して
Leaving warmth on my lips,
Goes to you
佇んで ボンネット
Standing there, by the hood,
加速しあげて
picking up speed.
喋りすぎよ 飽きてきたわ
You're talking too much, I'm getting bored,
Stay the twilight
似た瞳
Similar eyes...
解けかけた魔法
...the magic starts to unravel.
It's magic red
夏のあの目眩に 戻りたいの
I want to go back to that summer dizziness.
秘密を 飲もう
Let's drink the secret.
Maybe love stray my heart
さりげない 仕草して キスを
With a casual gesture, a kiss...
そらさず アイコンタクト
...without looking away, eye contact.
夕立に つきあいきれないわ
I can't keep up with this evening shower.
崩れてく 輪郭は
The crumbling silhouette
波のまにまに
drifts with the waves.
Maybe love stray my heart
何もかも 蜃気楼
Everything is a mirage,
夏の女神の気まぐれね
just a whim of the summer goddess.
いつかまたなんて I never say
I'll never say 'some other time'.
唇に裏腹
With contradictions on your lips,
残したままで
Leaving them just as they are.
La la la...
星みたいに隠れて
Hiding like a star,
I wanna be pin dot
天使はもっと脳裏に笑わない
The angel won't smile in my mind anymore.
顔も知らない人と目が合う今日この頃
These days, I lock eyes with people I don't know.
何かを指針にして動き始める歯車
The gears start turning, guided by something.
私の耳を劈くような
As if piercing through my ears,
音のない物ねだりだ夜が明ける頃
It's a silent plea for more as dawn approaches.
誰かの寝言が街を歩く頃
When someone's sleep-talking walks the streets,
あんなに傑作だ
It's such a masterpiece.
HELP!! このままじゃ生きられない
HELP!! I can't live like this.
だ、でも私いい子じゃいられない
But, I can't stay a good girl.
だから HELP!! 強がりをもっと起こしちゃえ
So HELP!! Let's bring out more of that bluff.
独りよがり泣き日も悪くないでしょ
Self-centered crying days aren't so bad, right?
流れ弾の数が増えていくから
As the number of stray bullets increases,
たまにあるラッキー邪魔に遭わない
Don't let the occasional luck get in the way.
名前も知らない人と目が合う今日この頃
These days, I lock eyes with nameless people.
何かを指針にして狂い始める歯車
The gears start going mad, guided by something.
夢見る時間に君がある事
That you exist in my dreaming time,
期待した分裏切られてクソだ
Is crap, being betrayed as much as I expected.
私じゃなきゃいけない理由は何処
Where's the reason it has to be me?
あんなに失敗作
Such a failure of a work.
HELP!! 大通りを歩きたい
HELP!! I want to walk the main street.
だ、でも私いい子じゃ終われない
But, I can't end as just a good girl.
だから HELP!! 臆病も魔が差しちゃえ
So HELP!! Let cowardice be tempted as well.
独りよがり情けなさを曝さば
If I expose my self-centered misery...
HELP!! Face blow away
Burn it all down away
いっそ喝采も合切も夢を見たい
I'd rather dream of applause and everything.
けど
But...
Mimpi terasa jauh
Dreams feel far away,
Sekejap mata pun bisa terhapus
Can be erased in the blink of an eye.
Can be erased in the blink of an eye,
Karena kita punya jiwa
Because we have a soul.
HELP!! このままじゃ楽しくない
HELP!! It's not fun like this.
だ、でも私傑作は手放したい
But, I want to let go of the masterpiece.
ほらね HELP!! 善も悪も全部愛してえかい
See? HELP!! Do you want to love all good and evil?
誰でも彼でも好き放題あそぼうじゃないか
Let's all just play however we want!
HELP!! このままじゃ生きられない
HELP!! I can't live like this.
だ、でも私いい子じゃいられない
But, I can't stay a good girl.
だから HELP!! 今だけを見つめてたい
So HELP!! I just want to stare at the now.
そう今だけを零さないように
So as not to spill this very moment.
単純で明快で
It's simple and clear,
混沌じゃない
Not chaos.
まだ想像と妄想と
Still with imagination, delusions,
偏見でFi?
And prejudice, Fi?
そりゃ完全な万全の
Isn't that a perfectly thorough
作戦じゃない？
Plan?
こっちに来てくれないか
Won't you come over here?
ハイハイお手上げ閉まっちゃってコーダ
Yes, yes, hands up, closing out to the coda.
ハイハイ期待感...
Yes, yes, this feeling of anticipation...
...ちゃってこう
...and let's go!
はいはいお姉さん しまっちゃってこう
Hey hey, big sister, let's wrap it up
はいはい期待完成おちゃってこう
Hey hey, expectation complete, let's keep it going
ホロホーク ホロホーク だけど
HoloHawk, HoloHawk, but
高嶺の花みたいに扱っちゃいや
Don't treat me like a flower on a high peak
あのね誰もかれも
You know, everyone and anyone
私と勘違い 驚きのアイ
Mistakes me for her, it's a surprising eye
ホロホーク ホロホーク だけど
HoloHawk, HoloHawk, but
ポンコツみがちょいあるだけで親近感
Just a bit of clumsiness gives a sense of familiarity
その際 その差異 その際
At that time, that difference, at that time
受け止めてよね 高嶺の未来 乾杯
Please accept it, cheers to the future of the high peak
しっかりワッチ
Watch closely
アイ マイ ユー ノー
I, my, you know
狩りとか苦手
I'm not good at hunting
巻き抜いて
Charge ahead
一見クールね
Look cool at first glance, right?
意外とギャップ系
Surprisingly full of gap moe
イメージ大変身
Image total makeover
OK
胎動の感触で 内緒じゃない
With the sensation of movement, it's not a secret
お先輩に相談に散々ねもう
Consulting seniors is quite an ordeal already
サヨナラ 野暮な配信じゃない
Goodbye, this isn't some boorish stream
ご静聴 解体正解
Thank you for listening, dismantling the correct answer
ホロホーク ホロホーク だけど
HoloHawk, HoloHawk, but
捕食しないさ だから怖がっちゃいや
I won't prey on you, so don't be afraid
ほらね爪も羽も お洒落に研いで
Look, I sharpen my claws and feathers stylishly
隠しちゃいない
And I'm not hiding them
ホロホーク ホロホーク だけど
HoloHawk, HoloHawk, but
観察眼がちょいあるだけで緊張感
Just a bit of observation skills gives a sense of tension
その際 その差異 その際
At that time, that difference, at that time
受け止めてよね 高まる時代 乾杯
Please accept it, cheers to the rising era
はいはいお姉さん しまっちゃってこう
Hey hey, big sister, let's wrap it up
はいはい期待完成おちゃってこう
Hey hey, expectation complete, let's keep it going
はいはいお姉さん しまっちゃってこう
Hey hey, big sister, let's wrap it up
はいはい期待完成おちゃってこう
Hey hey, expectation complete, let's keep it going
ホロホーク ホロホーク だけど
HoloHawk, HoloHawk, but
高嶺の花みたいに扱っちゃいや
Don't treat me like a flower on a high peak
あのね誰もかれも
You know, everyone and anyone
私と勘違い 驚きのアイ
Mistakes me for her, it's a surprising eye
ホロホーク ホロホーク だけど
HoloHawk, HoloHawk, but
ポンコツみがちょいあるだけで親近感
Just a bit of clumsiness gives a sense of familiarity
その際 その差異 その際
At that time, that difference, at that time
受け止めてよね 高嶺の未来 乾杯
Please accept it, cheers to the future of the high peak
アイちゃん 高まる時代 乾杯
Ai-chan, cheers to the rising era
What an amazing swing
作詞:TOPHAMHAT-KYO (FAKE TYPE.) 作曲:DYES IWASAKI (FAKE TYPE.)
Lyrics: TOPHAMHAT-KYO (FAKE TYPE.) Music: DYES IWASAKI (FAKE TYPE.)
What an amazing night!
Yes, it's a very nice!
OK, follow me, Whisper-Woppy flow!
わたわたしてられない 月がのぼって
Can't be flustered, the moon has risen
光るネオンライト 寝頃 夜がはじまる
Shining neon lights, the time for bed, the night begins
めぇめぇ泣いたって 月はもどらない
Even if I bleat "mee mee," the moon won't come back
ただ落込み 真暗に Dive? Not enough says
Just feeling down, dive into the pitch black? Not enough, it says
夢だけで見るなんてもったいないよね
It's a waste to only see it in dreams, right?
お利口さんたちが眠ってる間に 廻るマーベラス
While the good children are sleeping, a turning marvelous
君も目撃者になりたいでしょ？
You want to be a witness too, don't you?
呪文はYes ときめきなスイング
The spell is "Yes," a heart-throbbing swing
ハイテクノロジー 溶けてゆくこのシーン
High technology, this scene melting away
What amazing!
さながら宵の魔天楼 Foo Whaa!
Just like a skyscraper in the evening, Foo Whaa!
体感クラウドが日常から連れ出してあげましょう
Let the experiential cloud take you away from everyday life
さながら宵の魔天楼 Foo Whaa!
Just like a skyscraper in the evening, Foo Whaa!
たて たて 夢中になりましょ ど ど
Up, up, let's get obsessed, do do
まず自分が楽しまなくちゃパー
First, I have to enjoy myself, pah!
遠慮するなんてありえないのからー
Because holding back is out of the question!
喜びのお裾分けバイユー
Sharing the joy by you
ステージの上から バーンバーンバーン
From up on the stage, bang bang bang!
Yippee Yippee Yeah Yippee Yeah Yippee Yo Yeah
Sheep Yeah Sheep Yo Sheep Yeah Sheep Yeah Let's go!
ほらこっちおいで華やかな世界へおいで
Look, come over here, come to the glamorous world
お利口さんたちも眠っちゃいられない
Even the good children can't stay asleep
巻き込むマーベラス
A Marvelous that draws you in
四つのスイングマジック
Four swing magics
身体が勝手に反応し始めてるでしょ
Your body is starting to react on its own, isn't it?
最高のダンス
The best dance
What amazing!
さながら宵の魔天楼 Foo Whaa!
Just like a skyscraper in the evening, Foo Whaa!
体感クラウドが日常から連れ出してあげましょう
Let the experiential cloud take you away from everyday life
さながら宵の魔天楼 Foo Whaa!
Just like a skyscraper in the evening, Foo Whaa!
踊って 歌って
Dance and sing
肝っ玉 据わっちゃお
Let's get some guts
スパンコール着飾ら
Dressed up in sequins
見たままGorgeousなフロアなら
If the floor is as gorgeous as it looks
グローバルなこの差
This global difference
大好き完璧なリズムのDeedada
Love the perfect rhythm's deedada
観客も釘付けのピクセルばかり
The audience is fixed on pixels
ギリギリ悪くない尺八の音な
The sound of shakuhachi that's barely not bad
ゾンビもゾッコンさChao with the Border
Even zombies are obsessed, Chao with the Border
体温不足を移すくらい騒げAgain Again Again Again
Make enough noise to spread the lack of body heat Again Again Again Again
街中揺らして
Shake the city
音色をうずまいて
Swirl the tone
ステージをフル回転
Full rotation of the stage
Again! Swinging party up!
高まる気持ち待って
Wait for the rising feelings
Fuwa fuwa fuwa
眩しい色の非日常
A dazzling colored non-ordinary
トライに入れましょう
Let's try putting it in
全てをドキドキ待って
Wait for everything with a pounding heart
Fuwa fuwa fuwa
一生を一緒に輝くドッドッド
Shining through a lifetime together, Do-do-do
真っ白な世界に輝くドッドッド
Shining in a pure white world, Do-do-do
時間の海に浮かぶ島エッグヘッド
An island floating in the sea of time, Egghead
世界変える未来島ラボフェイズ
The future island that changes the world, Labo Phase
最高なのを創るの 叶えたい願望
Creating the best thing, the desire I want to fulfill
未来のお宝 探し出しちゃおう
Let's find the treasures of the future
天才が引き起こす 発想の奇跡
A miracle of ideas brought about by a genius
脳内で終わらせない 夢のファンタジー
A dream fantasy that doesn't end in the brain
世界をひっくり返す テクノロジー
Technology that turns the world upside down
叶えちゃう ラボラトリー
Fulfilling it, Laboratory
導かれる末路 幾何学
The fate led by geometry
悟り得よう 6人のサテライト
Let's gain enlightenment, the six satellites
湧き出すアイデア 止まらない
Gushing ideas won't stop
忙しすぎて 猫の手も借りたい
Too busy, I want to borrow even a cat's paw
海も波も越えていく 海賊王
Crossing the sea and waves, Pirate King
常識を変えていく 発明家よ
Oh inventor who changes common sense
そんな奴らに 憧れてきた
I've come to admire such people
次は誰か 王になる
Next, someone will become king
無限の夢 未来の知恵
Infinite dreams, future wisdom
ひらめきを巻き起こせ
Bring about inspiration
無限の夢 未来の知恵
Infinite dreams, future wisdom
過去も世界も飛び越して
Leap over the past and the world
VEGAPUNK 生み出せよアイデア
VEGAPUNK, bring forth ideas
VEGAPUNK 革命よ ここから
VEGAPUNK, revolution starts from here
時間の海に浮かぶ島エッグヘッド
An island floating in the sea of time, Egghead
世界変える未来島ラボフェイズ
The future island that changes the world, Labo Phase
This mind is undefeated Until my goal's completed
Let's keep on searching for The treasure of the come
Let's keep on searching for The treasure yet to come
Genius Ideas that keep us free
Mysterious Passions burning inside of me
Delirious Channeling new technology
Here we come Laboratory just for the scene
Transitions of evil The contents of my mind
Knowledge through violence 6 satellites
Ideas can't stop rushing out Thinking they might use
I'm too busy working into the night
The pirate king who braves the ocean while in search of a vision
A ruler of invention that can modify all reason
That's what I've been dreaming to something I'm gonna be
Next of all I'm gonna do
無限の夢 未来の知恵
Infinite dreams, future wisdom
ひらめきを巻き起こせ
Bring about inspiration
無限の夢 未来の知恵
Infinite dreams, future wisdom
過去も世界も飛び越して
Leap over the past and the world
VEGAPUNK 生み出せよアイデア
VEGAPUNK, bring forth ideas
VEGAPUNK 革命よ ここから
VEGAPUNK, revolution starts from here
言うこと聞かなきゃ 振りかざす正義
If you don't listen, brandish justice
世界守る 軍団の体面
The prestige of the legion protecting the world
秘密巡る 怪しげな企み
Suspicious schemes surrounding secrets
心の奥に 隠された狂気
The madness hidden deep within the heart
真実を追う 危険な勇気
Dangerous courage to pursue the truth
謎に満ちた 夢のエネルギー
Dream energy full of mysteries
天才が見せる 世界の形
The shape of the world shown by a genius
どこへ向かう 未来の島エッグヘッド
Where is the future island Egghead headed?
はい注目！ マジチョーどっ高価
Attention! Seriously super expensive
センキュー！ 着てんのは
Thank you! What I'm wearing is...
あーね！ 君たちの声まだ足りてないんじゃないの？
Ah, I see! Your voices aren't enough yet, are they?
Our night's just begun! Let's blast off!
赤赤火照るぜ
Burning red hot
一皮剥けちゃってから結べ
Tie it up after you've shed a skin
渇いた喉うるおすオアシスよまりん
The oasis to quench your dry throat, it's Marine!
あはは
Ahaha!
ただのでいいでしょ？
Just the usual is fine, right?
OK!
From shore to shore, my moves bring the storm to the floor
Thunder race, that's a sonic boom
I rap the beat like I'm serving shockwave
Up down need no sunblock
I can make it rain 'cause you hit the jackpot
Baby, get ready if you wanna ride with the OGs
あっちちの舞台 渡れ Get ready!
Cross the scorching hot stage, Get ready!
ハンズアップ ブチ上げて前 Get ready!
Hands up, get pumped up, Get ready!
クラっと来ちゃうような 熱が足りない
Not enough heat to make you dizzy
Our night just begun, let's blast it!
弾けて果てに歌え Get ready!
Burst out and sing to the end, Get ready!
Life summarize, everyone a party Get ready!
All eyes on me, I can taste the higher
えい 待って待って 沸いてこうぜ
Hey, wait wait, let's get hyped!
ハイ 注目前へ ちょー待って此処
Hey, attention forward, wait a second here
千九十点の輪 あ あ あ
The circle of 1090 points, ah, ah, ah
よそ見してんじゃん マリンがベスデスガールじゃん
You're looking away, Marine is the best-est girl, right?
砂の数よりも魅力が 君たちもねぇ 虜でしょ？
More charm than grains of sand, you're all captivated, aren't you?
星の数ほどって誰か言った？ 大人の魅力よ 手を繋ごら
Did someone say 'as many as stars'? It's adult charm, hold my hand
マリンは17だ！ 手を引けよら 我慢の限界かな とか言って
Marine is 17! Pull my hand, saying 'is this the limit of my patience?'
Bringing heat that can't be splashed away
Vision big catch to stardom I deserve
And I'm just chilling, a mocktail I'm sipping 'cause I got that juice, might let you have a taste
見てこのバディ Money is so honey 基本素肌ね
Look at this body, money is so honey, basically bare skin, right?
休まないで待って Set a bonfire Always take you higher Make you drive you crazy!
Don't rest, wait, set a bonfire, always take you higher, make you drive you crazy!
あはは 暑苦しくなってこう もうどうしようもない
Ahaha, let's get even hotter, it's unstoppable now
My bright spotlight, don't don't stop and catch it is so
あっちちの舞台 渡れ Get ready!
Cross the scorching hot stage, Get ready!
ハンズアップ ブチ上げて前 Get ready!
Hands up, get pumped up, Get ready!
クラっと来ちゃうような 熱が足りない
Not enough heat to make you dizzy
Our night just begun, let's blast it!
弾けて果てに歌え Get ready!
Burst out and sing to the end, Get ready!
Life summarize, everyone a party Get ready!
All eyes on me, I can taste the higher
えい 待って待って 沸いてこうぜ
Hey, wait wait, let's get hyped!
ハイ 注目前へ ちょー待って此処
Hey, attention forward, wait a second here
千九十点の輪 あ あ あ
The circle of 1090 points, ah, ah, ah
Bring it back, let's hit it one more time!
私達マジで最強じゃん Just too besties of life あ あ あ
We're truly the strongest, just two besties of life, ah, ah, ah
キャスト
Cast
セットリスト
Setlist
「Capture the Moment」(Instrumental)
"Capture the Moment" (Instrumental)
ホロライブ、オフィシャルカードゲーム！
hololive Official Card Game!
ステージに立つ、個性溢れるホロメンたちが織りなす...
On the stage, unique hololive members weave together...
無限の可能性を秘めた、多彩なコラボレーション。
A diverse collaboration with infinite possibilities.
そこに、新たな色が交わる時。
When new colors join them,
心を惹きつける、5つの音色が響き渡る。
five captivating melodies will resonate.
さあ、君も私たちと一緒に、色彩溢れる戦場へ！
Come on, join us on the colorful battlefield!
ブースターパック「クインテット・スペクトラム」発売中！
Booster Pack "Quintet Spectrum" now on sale!
スタートデッキ3種も同時発売！！
Three types of Start Decks are also available!!
公式アプリ『ホロプラス』の魅力を聞いてみた！
We asked about the charm of the official app, "holoplus"!
マイ推しの最新情報が通知される！
Get notifications for your "oshi's" latest info!
ホロジュールがすぐ開けるので配信を見逃さない！
Open "holojour" instantly so you never miss a stream!
色々な地域の仲間とコメントやいいねで共感できるあったかい空間！
A warm space where you can connect with friends through comments and likes!
あなたのコメントが企画に！？公式番組『ホロの休日（仮）』
Your comments could become part of a project!? Official program "Holo no Kyujitsu (Working Title)"
販売終了間近のグッズが分かる！グッズ情報案内板などなど！
Find out about goods nearing the end of sales! Goods Information Board, and more!
うわ〜！他にもこんなにたくさん！
Whoa! There's so much more!
すごい！
Amazing!
ぜひ、あなたのホロ活にプラスしませんか？
Why not add it to your hololive fandom life?
ここからインストールできます！
You can install it from here!
ホロプラスで待ってますね！
I'll be waiting for you on holoplus!
はあちゃま、はい。あーん。
Haachama, here. Say "ah".
急に何？
What's this all of a sudden?
いいから、いいから。
It's okay, just try it.
普通においしい！
It's actually delicious!
ちょっと形が崩れただけだもん。落ち込むことないよ。
It just lost its shape a little bit. There's no need to feel down.
はあちゃまが頑張ってくれたの知ってるから。ちょっとずつ一緒に覚えていこうよ。
I know how hard you worked on it. Let's learn together, little by little.
ね？
Okay?
えっ... うん。
Eh... Yeah.
それじゃあ、次コロッケ作る時は、オリジナルのレシピを考えておくわ。
Well then, the next time I make croquettes, I'll come up with an original recipe.
きっともっとおいしくなるわよ！
I'm sure they'll be even tastier!
やだ。
No thanks.
なんでよ！はあちゃまならもっとおいしく...
Why not!? If it's Haachama, they'll be even better...
やだ
No!
なんでよ！はあちゃまならもっとおいしく...
Why not?! If it's Haachama, she'll make it even more delicious...
ダメ
No way.
異世界ドタバタクッキングコメディ！
An otherworldly slapstick cooking comedy!
ホロアース・デイズ・ア・テイル・サイド・ダブル...
Holoearth Days A Tale Side:W...
ウェスタ・デ・クッキング、幸せのルセット...
Westa de Cooking - Shiawase no Recette...
大好評連載中！
Now being serialized to great acclaim!
出演タレントが選んだ お気に入りコマTシャツが登場！
Favorite manga panel T-shirts selected by the talents are here!
累計10万部突破記念！！ 『ヤマト神想怪異譚』 お気に入りコマTシャツ
Commemorating over 100,000 copies sold!! 'Yamato Shinsou Kaiitan' Favorite Panel T-Shirts
hololive SUPER EXPO 2025
今年のテーマは...
This year's theme is...
hololive ARCADE!
[STAGE1] ARCADEをテーマにした展示空間
[STAGE 1] Exhibition space themed around ARCADE
[STAGE2] グッズやフード、それにステージ！
[STAGE 2] Merch, food, and stages!
[STAGE3] もちろんコスプレOK！
[STAGE 3] Cosplay is allowed, too!
and...
ホロライブプロダクション全員がARCADEをテーマにした
8色のパーカー衣装で登場！
All members of hololive production will appear
in 8 colors of hoodie outfits based on the ARCADE theme!
そして... 9色目のパーカーを着るのは...
And... the one wearing the 9th color hoodie is...
あなた！！！
YOU!!!
ホロライブメンバーたちと一緒に協力して、競って、遊び倒そう！
Let's cooperate, compete, and play to our hearts' content with the hololive members!
hololive SUPER EXPO 2025
2025.3.8(sat) - 3.9(sun)
March 8-9, 2025 (Sat-Sun)
個性の光が色彩となり、響き合う。
The light of individuality becomes color and resonates together.
私たちのステージは、今、鮮やかに色づきはじめる。
Our stage is now beginning to take on vibrant colors.
hololive 6th fes. Color Rise Harmony
ホロライブ史上最大の...
The largest in hololive history...
幕張メッセ 国際展示場 9-11ホールを使った 大規模fes.
A large-scale festival utilizing Halls 9-11 of Makuhari Messe International Exhibition Hall.
hololive STAGE1
hololive STAGE 1
hololive STAGE2
hololive STAGE 2
hololive STAGE3
hololive STAGE 3
多くのクリエイターが生み出した名曲の数々を、
The many masterpieces created by numerous creators will be
多彩なホロライブメンバーたちの表現力で 再び披露する特別なステージ。
performed once again through the expressive power of various hololive members on this special stage.
CREATORS' STAGE
さあ、心を響かせ、
Now, let your heart resonate,
あなたの色をこのハーモニーに加えてください。
and please add your color to this harmony.
hololive 6th fes. Color Rise Harmony
2025.3.8(sat) - 3.9(sun)
March 8-9, 2025 (Sat-Sun)